ZiMuZu
倾情奉献
翻译
草草
磁芯章鱼X
翻译
滚成一个团子
木浅
翻译
showeryhe
小酸奶!
翻译
冬麟
某羽
翻译
潇湘月影
时间轴
Kallen   今
特效
宝宝   草草
电脑狂人
第二季
第四集
校对&总监
草草
后期
饿得慌
顾问
somehacker
你们知道为什么早上要先吃蔬菜吗
You know why vegetables are a better way to start your morning?
因为蔬菜富含纤维素  有助消化
Because they contain fiber, which helps with your digestion.
你们知道消化是什么吗
You know what that is?
我刚刚解过大手了  我能吃甜玉米麦片吗
I just did number two. Can I have Frosted Flakes?
还记得我们谈过要尝试新东西吗
Remember our little talk about trying new things?
37度  穿衣服准备上学
98.7. Get dressed for school.
妈妈  我还是不舒服
Mommy, I still don't feel well
可爸爸还是要逼我上学
and Daddy's making me go to school.
宝贝  妈妈现在可不能染上病
Sweetheart, Mommy really can't afford to get sick right now.
我来给你冲咖啡
Let me make you a pot of coffee.
多谢  但我得赶紧去办公室了
Oh, thanks, but I gotta get to the office.
你能试试我的额头吗
Could you feel my forehead?
我担心我可能染上琼妮的病了
I'm afraid I'm coming down with whatever Joanie has.
她已经好了
Had.
非常凉  和你一样酷
Cool as a cucumber, just like you.
行了  你知道我要迟到了
Come on, you know I'm late.
好  我明白了
All right, I get it.
戈登  我没不高兴  我真的要晚了
Gordon, I'm not mad. I really am late.
我知道  我可不想耽误你上班
No, I know. I don't want you to be late for work.
多谢您百忙之中抽空见我
Uh, thank you for squeezing me into your schedule.
不客气  正式上班前你随便讲
Happy to. You've got my ear until the day begins in earnest.
-你想说什么  -机会
- What's on your mind? - Opportunity.
我先打断你一下
Well, let me stop you there.
我这里可没有任何职缺
I don't have any job openings.
没有正好  我也不想调职
Well, that works out well because I don't want a job.
你眼皮底下埋着一座大金矿
You're sitting on a gold mine.
给我六个月  我就能把网络和计算机系统部
Give me six months, I'll turn Network and Computer Systems
转变成可以创收的部门
into an income-generating department.
那好  我洗耳恭听
Okay, I'll play.
我就在主机室旁边工作
I work right next to the mainframe sites.
这些机器每天都是全天候通电
They're powered on all day, every day.
晚上和周末  他们就干放在那里
On nights and weekends, they're just sitting there idle.
我们可以在下班时间
We lease our mainframe space
把我们的主机和网络设备
and our network during off hours
租赁给需要
to third-party businesses
更大更强的网络的第三方
who need a larger, more powerful network.
费用几乎为零  所得全是纯收益
Overhead is near zero. It's pure profit.
安全风险太大了
It's too big a security risk.
我们的主机上运行着不少敏感的业务
We have sensitive business transactions running on our mainframe.
是这样  你不明白主机是怎么工作的
Now, see, you don't understand how a mainframe works.
我们可以修改优先级设定
We can configure the privilege settings
严格控制这些用户的权限
to lock these users into a tightly controlled area.
可以想象成是一个隔离室
Think of it as a padded cell.
外部用户绝对无法接触到公司的内部信息
No outside user can access our company files.
而这只是开始
And that's just the beginning.
这个部门可以
This department would be
催生出一个大规模的项目
an incubator for a large-scale operation.
我们可以把这尊巨人
We can turn this juggernaut
转化成一个强大而先进的独立实体
into one massive, forward-thinking entity
到时  你就能和雅各布·维勒称兄道弟了
and you, you'll be on a first-name basis with Jacob Wheeler.
我们只需要敢于去想  敢下决心
All we have to do is imagine it, trust it,
敢于动手
and flip the switch.
如果你这么坚信这个主意对西方集团有好处
If you believe so much in this vision for Westgroup,
那何不和你准岳父说呢
why don't you share it with your future father-in-law?
我知道你是谁
Oh, I know who you are.
你不会真以为我随随便便
You didn't think I'd take a meeting
就会见一个数据中心的小职员吧
with some plebe from the data center, did you?
她第一次离婚之前我就在这里了
I was here before her first marriage blew up
等她跟你掰了  我还会在这里
and I'll be here after she's done with you, too.
-你准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready for this? - Yeah.
-你先讲话  然后我...  -我知道
- So do your thing and then I'll-- - Yeah, I got it.
我想感谢大家伙儿
Okay, so, I just wanted to thank everyone
最近这几天忙得死去活来
for busting their asses the last few days,
基本没捞着睡觉
pretty much without sleep.
大家都知道我们最近情况不乐观
It's no secret that we're struggling,
这并非是这里任何人的责任
through no fault of anyone here,
但我们目前运营艰难
to keep the lights on.
每一分钱都很重要
Every penny counts,
谢谢大家这么配合
so thank you, guys, for being such good sports.
我们并没结束  但确实已命悬一线
It's not game over, but we are on life support.
我们仅用三分之一的XT维持运转
We're operating with a third of our XTs
我们的用户纷纷取消订阅
and our subscribers keep cancelling.
看来在游戏玩家中没有忠诚可言
I don't know, I guess there's no honor among gamers.
所以我们...
So we're kind of...
我们现在入不敷出
Look, we're spending more than we're making,
这是个数学...
which is a mathematical...
我们几乎没钱了
We're almost out of money.
仅有的资金要用来维持运营
What little we have we need to cover operating costs,
也就是说
so what that means is that
我们现在付不起你们的工资了
we can't afford to pay your salaries right now.
但作为交换  如果你们不拿工资
But in exchange for you forgoing your salaries,
我们会给你们公司股份
we're offering you shares of the company,
长远来讲  价值其实更高
which will be worth a lot more in the long run.
-成功的话  -对
- In success. - Yes.
对  成功的话
Yes, in success.
这就是我们选择的事业
Look, this is what we all signed up for.
这就是在这种公司工作的风险
It's the risk of working at a company like this,
但别忘记  好处也多很多
but don't forget that the upside is also so much greater.
我觉得值得冒这个险
I think it's a risk worth taking,
但你们每个人都要自己做决定
but each of you need to decide that for yourself.
我加入
I'm in.
我也是
Me, too.
Yep.
加入
In.
我退出
I'm out.
别这样  哥们
C-come on, man.
这段经历很愉快
It's been a sweet ride.
有学生贷款  抱歉
Student loans, sorry.
我们可以谈谈吗
Hey, can we talk about this?
我不会为了网络游戏冒这种险
I'm not going to take that kind of risk on a bunch of online games.
祝你写卡带游戏愉快
Have fun writing cartridges.
那是你一直想做的
That's what you've always wanted to do,
我不过给了你个好借口
so I just gave you an easy excuse.
也许是我觉得那些股份不会值什么钱的
Or maybe I don't think the shares are gonna be worth anything.
连续两天了
Two days in a row.
怎么  你想回来工作吗
What, are you angling to come back to work?
工作  你可是一个子都不付
Work? You ain't paying anybody anything.
更像是做义工
More like volunteerin'.
不  我正好有事来这边
No, I had an errand to run this side of town.
就想给你们带点早餐玉米饼
Thought I'd bring you over some breakfast tacos
你们的惨象都快赶上战俘了
'cause y'all are starting to look like POWs around here.
然后我发现了你们的发票夹
And I noticed this file with your invoices in it and
以及一些可以缩减开支的地方
a couple places where you could cut some costs popped out at me.
如果你想听听我的建议的话
If you're interested in hearing my suggestions.
当然
Yeah.
够了  我要回去弄游戏了
That's it, I'm going back to games.
别啊  莱夫  你做得很好
Oh, no, Lev, you're doing great.
你可以搞定的  只有6个聊天室
You can handle this. It's just six rooms.
18个
18.
你真是没听我说话
You really do tune me out.
不会吧  怎么会这样
Come on, how did that happen?
你说如果有许多人在聊同一主题
You told me any time there's a lot of chatter on a subject
就为那些用户创建一个新聊天室
to create a new room for those users.
这真是难以置信  莱夫
This is really incredible, Lev.
我刚创建完一个新聊天室
I just finished creating a new room
现在有一群喂鸟器爱好者
and now a bunch of bird feeder enthusiasts
挤在猫奴聊天室里讨论把猫砂
have hijacked the Catty Cathys to discuss using cat litter
-放在喂鸟器底端  -让我看看
- in the bottom of bird feeders. - Let me see, let me see.
结果现在猫奴聊天室的用户很生气
So now the Catty Cathys are pissed off
因为他们不能继续聊去尿味的话题了
because they can't follow their urine odor removal thread,
这让我很恼火  因为我讨厌猫和这群话唠
which pisses me off because I hate cats and Chatty Cathys.
我们有用户进聊天室只为了发牢骚吗
We have users coming into our rooms just to complain?
我们有没有只为社区而注册的用户呢
Do we have people signing up just for Community?
需要我给你画个爱猫女士和游戏玩家的维恩图吗
Do you need me to draw you a Venn diagram of cat ladies and gamers?
利用图形的交合来表示
多个集合之间的逻辑关系
重叠区为零
Not a whole lot of overlap.
我们能问卡梅伦再要个社区管理员吗
Now can we please ask Cameron for another body?
等有30个聊天室了告诉我
When we get up to 30 rooms, you let me know.
我们已经寄出了
We already sent out mailers
有软件重装说明的邮件广告
with instructions on reinstalling the software.
-但他们还在取消订阅  -当然了
- They're still cancelling. - Well, of course they are.
你把淋病传给女朋友了
You just gave your girlfriend the clap.
你觉得几封邮件就能弥补吗
You think sendin' out mailers is gonna fix that?
你得送花  青霉素可没用
You gotta send her flowers, not penicillin.
那你说怎么办
What do you suggest we do?
首先  你们需要修复公司形象
First of all, your image needs rehabilitation.
我看到有张发票
I noticed an invoice here
是《字节》杂志的预付广告位
for prepaid ad space in "Byte Magazine."
利用广告来改变形象
Look, use this to change the story.
听起来不错  但我们雇不起广告公司
That sounds great, but we can't afford an ad agency right now.
不  你们不需要广告公司
No, you don't need one.
就两个大号黑体字  招聘
Two words in bold black lettering-- we're hiring.
看到这个  人们会觉得你们现在风生水起
Folks see that, they think you're cooking on the front burner.
再加上点色彩  也许会更好
Look, and a little splash of color would be nice in there somewhere.
吸引目光  也不会花很多钱
Draw the eye, won't break the bank.
嗯  可以贴张员工工作照
Yeah, maybe a photo of our staff at work.
那绝对显眼
Yeah, that'll really pop.
博迪和神童趴在键盘上埋头苦干
What, Bodie and Wonderboy hunched over their keyboards?
也许能让人们想到
Yeah, or it'll remind people
史蒂夫·乔布斯在车库创办苹果的事呢
of Steve Jobs starting Apple in his garage.
这事总是能引起人们的兴趣
People can't seem to get enough of that old chestnut.
不能再电话推销了  你得挨家挨户上门谈
No more cold calls. You've got to go door-to-door.
-博斯  没那么多人手  -冲大鱼下手
- Boz, we don't have the manpower. - Just go after the whales.
大鱼  最大的客户
Your whales, your top dogs.
我标出来的这十个名字
Those 10 names that I highlighted here,
是你们最大的买家
these are your biggest spenders.
就从他们入手
Start with them.
好吧  我想可以派莱夫去
Uh, okay, I guess we could send Lev out.
他看起来比较正常
He k-kind of passes for normal.
不行  我需要莱夫帮我做社区呢
Oh, no, no, I need Lev for Community.
-为什么  -我们有近20个聊天室了
- Why? - We're up to almost 20 rooms.
-什么  好多  -是啊
- What? That's huge. - I know,
这算是个好消息吧
that's a little bit of good news, right?
什么时候的事
W-when did that happen?
就今早上  他给我看了...
Just this morning. He showed me--
女士们  现在你们该说
Ladies, this is where you say,
"你能帮我们办这件事吗  博斯沃思
"Could you please do this for us, Bosworth?
你可是个传奇推销员呢"
"You are an unbelievable salesman."
我说  "不  那已经是过去的我了"
And I say, "No, that chapter in my life is closed."
你们说  "拜托  就帮我们这一次吧"
And then you say, "Please do us this favor?"
我说  "不  我不能"
And I say, "No, I cannot."
我们就这样你来我往几次
And then it goes back and forth like that a couple more times
然后我再答应
and I say yes.
谢谢
Thanks.
接下来交给我吧
I can take it from here.
这要怎么往工作订单上写
What am I supposed to write on the work order?
需要写吗
What work order?
怎么了  今天怎么只有我说啊
What's going on? Why am I the only one pitching today, guys?
天高任我行  不管什么想法都行
Come on, sky's the limit. Whatever-- whatever comes to mind.
各位  认真点
Come on, guys, let's get serious.
免得丢了股权
There's shares on the line here.
来吧
Yeah.
我们可以模仿《冰城传奇》出个游戏
Uh, we could do our version of "Bard's Tale,"
设定玩家要救的公主
but the players try to free a princess
其实是霍比特人乔装的
who's actually a Hobbit in disguise.
好吧  我觉得我们应该放宽思路
Okay, I think we need to go bigger.
也许是我没说清楚
Uh, maybe I'm not explaining it very well.
就是  玩家们...
You see, the players, um--
不如我们设计一款射击游戏
What if we create a shooter game
要完全拟真的
that's totally immersive?
从玩家的视角展现周围环境
That shows the player's perspective of his surroundings.
-你想在线上这么做  -对  怎么了
- And you want to try to do this online? - Yeah. What?
我清楚我们目前能达到的图像效果有限
I mean, I know we're more limited in the kind of graphics we can do,
但如果做成了  肯定很棒
but if we pulled it off, it would be amazing.
设置什么样的敌人  不要坦克外星人
Uh, what's a good enemy? And no tanks or aliens.
来些新点子
We need something fresh.
-早上好  -抱歉来晚了
- Morning. - Sorry, I got held up.
你还可以提前下班
Okay, leave a little earlier.
-有了  -说
- Okay, I... I got it. - Yeah.
赶在ET吃你的锐滋豆前找到并杀了它
Find and kill E.T. before he eats your Reese's Pieces.
不行
No!
博迪  太差劲了
Bodie, that's, like, the worst.
想不出来就散会吧
Okay, let's stop while we're stuck
明天再讨论
and then we can pick up again tomorrow.
好吧
Good?
那个简直
Well, that was...
博迪  这主意糟透了
Bodie, it was a bad idea.
他想吃糖果就随他  怎么能杀ET
He will eat candy. You cannot kill E.T.
只是锐滋豆啊
It's just some Reese's Pieces.
要不你也住进来  会不会好点
Sorry, would you be more comfortable in one of the bedrooms?
不用  我很好  补充点能量就好
No, no, I'm good. I just need to fuel up.
-你怎么了  -没事
- What's going on with you? - Nothing.
就是睡过头了
I just-- I slept through my alarm
可能真的太累了
and I guess I'm just really tired.
我们都很累
Okay, we're all really tired.
不能因为没工资拿了
Just because you're not getting paid anymore
就上班迟到
doesn't mean you can show up late for work.
-影响士气  -不会再犯了
- It's bad for morale. - It won't happen again.
-好的  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
我都没看到你
I didn't see you there.
-等很久了吗  -才到
- You been waiting long? - Just got here.
我刚在跑步
Oh, I was out doing my miles.
跑了9英里
Did-- did nine miles.
来杯冰沙吗  我自己也要弄一杯喝
You want a smoothie? I'm making one for myself.
好  你什么时候开始喝冰沙了
Sure. When did you start drinking smoothies?
稍等  我走近点
Hold on, let me get closer.
之前说要健康生活
I wasn't kidding there when I told you
我可没开玩笑
I was getting back into shape.
1985对我是重要的一年
You know, 1985's my year, man.
饮食均衡  勤加锻炼
I'm eating better, I'm exercising.
我好久没长期慢跑了
You know, I haven't jogged regularly since,
都记不得有多久了
I mean, I don't even know.
阿迪达斯推出了这套田径服
Adidas came out with that track suit.
是啊  已经值了
Exactly. It's already paying off, too.
昨天医生来电说  我的血液检查结果很好
Doctor called yesterday, said that my blood work's good.
身体状态就像25岁的人一样
Said I've got the body of a 25-year-old.
好了
All right.
我编程了这个遥控装置
I programmed the remote
可以打开家里所有电器
to turn on all the electrical appliances in the house.
挺有创意的吧
Pretty innovative, huh?
我也在西方集团能源做一些革新性的工作
You know, I've been doing some innovative stuff at Westgroup Energy.
石油产业正遭受重创  需要多样化
Oil's taking a big hit and the industry needs to diversify, so...
这是把西方集团带进信息时代的绝佳时机
It's a perfect moment to take Westgroup into the Information Age.
听说过分时吗
Um, have you heard about time-sharing?
听说过
Yeah, I've heard of time-sharing.
西方集团有一台全新的IBM 3090主机
Westgroup's got a brand-spankin'-new IBM 3090 mainframe
仍在公测阶段  放在市区总部
still in beta at headquarters downtown.
先从那里入手
I'm starting there
下一步就是伦敦和纽约的3081主机
and then moving to the 3081 in London and New York.
天呐  利润率肯定很大
Wow, shit. Profit margins will be huge.
是啊  比起来  阿帕网就像个土电话
Yeah, it'll make ARPANET look like two tin cans and a fishing line.
我需要一个底层工程师
So I'm looking for a ground-floor engineer
修改主机配置  实现外部接入
to convert the mainframes for outside dial-in access.
慢着  你不是在挖我吧
Wait, you're not trying to sell me on this, are you?
不  我们只是聊聊  你太多心了
No, we're just talking. You're reading too much into it.
我要找个人  你是我认识的最棒的工程师
I'm looking for someone. You're the best engineer I know.
我想先来问过你
I wanted to give you the first right of refusal.
你应该高兴
Be flattered.
我是很高兴  而且我拒绝
I am flattered, all right? And I refuse.
-我还以为咱们处得不错呢  -的确不错
- I thought we were getting along. - We are getting along.
不要谈合作了  免得毁了这份关系
Let's not ruin it by jumping back into business together.
来嘛  就干一天
Come on, it's one day's work.
他们用的还是卡迪夫系统的软件
They're still running Cardiff Systems software.
你闭着眼睛都能搞定
You could do it with your eyes closed.
你上周邀请我和唐娜共进晚餐
When you invited me and Donna to dinner last week,
是为了讨好我  让我帮你吗
was that to butter me up for this?
我请你们吃饭的时候还没想到这个呢
I didn't even have this idea when I invited you to dinner.
莎拉是你未婚妻吗
Is Sara even your fiance,
还是你雇来的
or is that just some person that you hired
好让别人觉得你正常  值得信任
to make yourself seem normal and trustworthy?
这话听起来太疯狂了
Now you just sound crazy.
不  疯狂是一遍遍重复做同样的事
No, crazy is doing the same thing over and over again
还指望得到不同的结果
and expecting a different result.
你知道这个技术领域正在爆炸性增长吧
You do understand this area of tech is exploding, right?
过个一年半  咱们的规模会比计算机服务大五倍
In 18 months, we'll be bigger than CompuServe by a power of five.
你一年半后会在哪里
Where will you be in 18 months?
不好说
I don't know.
也许花着我靠巨人赚来的钱
Maybe drinking mai tais poolside in Maui
躺在毛伊岛的泳池边喝鸡尾酒
off all the money I made on the Giant.
对不起  乔  你还是找别人吧
I'm sorry, Joe. You're gonna have to find somebody else.
-小伙子  你爸爸在家吗  -没在家
- Oh, hey there, son. Is your daddy home? - No.
他什么时候回来
When do you expect him?
这问题谁都想知道呢
Well, that's the million-dollar question.
不管你卖什么  我都没兴趣
Look, whatever you're selling, I'm not interested.
夫人  我不是来卖东西的
Ma'am, I'm not selling anything.
我名叫约翰·博斯沃思
My name's John Bosworth, by the way.
我是一家叫穆特尼的公司的客户满意度部主管
I'm head of Customer Satisfaction at a company called Mutiny.
我今早过来  只是想向您儿子
I just came by this morning to apologize to your son here
为这周网络的扰动而道歉
about all our network hassles this week
并想办法劝他回到穆特尼的大家庭里
and see what I can do to bring him back into the Mutiny family.
不必了  是我取消了订阅
Nothing. I'm the one that cancelled the subscription, okay?
他用我的信用卡刷了上百美元
He's been racking up hundreds of dollars on my credit card.
我都不记得他多久没往家里带学校的小伙伴了
Can't remember the last time that he had a friend home from school.
我是说...
I mean...
你们这些电子游戏公司和毒贩子差不多
You video game companies are no better than drug peddlers.
对不起  夫人  没想到我们的服务
Oh, I'm sorry, ma'am. I didn't realize our services
影响了您儿子的社交生活
had disrupted your boy's social life.
-你几年级了  孩子  -九年级
- What grade are you in, son? - Ninth.
你妈妈说得对
Yeah, your mama's right.
你应该多花点时间和学校里的朋友玩
You gotta spend more time with your buddies at school.
他们只会聊体育
All they talk about is sports.
不是这样的  加文呢
Well, that's not true. What about Gavin?
你有和穆特尼的用户成为朋友吗
Have any of these Mutiny users become friends of yours?
有  大概32个吧
Oh, yeah, like 32.
就是经常和我聊天的
Well, that I talk to regularly.
有六七个只想跟我一较高下
Maybe six or seven that just want to play against me,
但是也挺有意思的
which is also fun.
我都不懂你是怎么跟那帮人交流的
I don't understand how you're talking to all these people.
你玩电脑时明明一句话都不说啊
I never hear a peep out of you when you're down there.
我妈妈是个老古董
My mother's a Luddite.
我们给对方发送信息
We type messages to each other.
网上就是这么交流的
That's how you talk online.
太太  我们俩都太过时了  没法理解他们
Ma'am, you and I are too old school to understand this,
但对于您儿子和他的朋友来说
but to your son here and his friends,
穆特尼就是他们的教堂
Mutiny is the church.
他们能在那里找到与自己志同道合的人
It's where they find community.
有时候也只在那里能找到
Sometimes that's the only place.
祝二位今天愉快
You have a good day.
不好意思耽搁了您这么久
I'm sorry to have taken up so much of your time.
等等  你说你叫什么来着
Wait, um, what'd you say your name was again?
约翰
It's John.
约翰·博斯沃思
John Bosworth.
你在找我吗
I heard you were looking for me?
是的
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um,
我在做清点
okay, so I've been doing some inventory,
想看看我们能放弃哪些游戏
trying to figure out what games we can afford to lose
来减轻网络负担
to help lighten the network.
好主意  你想要我的建议还是...
That's smart. Did you want suggestions or...
我在想
Well, I was thinking that
双陆棋和西洋跳棋必须砍
Backgammon and Checkers are no-brainers.
这两个用户最少  也不是我们原创的
They're our lowest performers and not one of our originals.
是啊  说得很对
Yeah, that's great.
而且我还得关掉社区
And I'm gonna have to cut Community.
-为什么  -这个嘛
- Why? - Well...
社区唯一占用的带宽是用户打字
The only bandwidth it takes up is people on it typing,
而打字最快的人也快不过最慢的电话调制器
and no one types as fast as even the slowest telephone modem.
与带宽无关  而是安全问题
It's not about bandwidth. It's about security.
社区最容易受攻击
Community's our most vulnerable spot.
有人分享了问题文件我们就会再次受影响
Someone shares the wrong file, we get infected again.
我不能冒险再出现这样的事
I just-- I can't take a chance on that happening.
如果你想让社区成为大家交流的地方
If you want to make this a place where people can connect,
那么就必然有风险
then there's going to be risk involved.
我知道
I know.
我不想为这么小的项目冒险
I'm just not willing to take a risk on something so small.
一周之内用户增加到原来的三倍
We've tripled in a week.
许多用户都不是游戏玩家
A lot of our users aren't even gamers
维护起来又只需要很少的人力
and it requires very little manpower,
所以我得跟你说实话
so I have to be honest with you,
我认为从商业角度来看
I think this is a huge mistake
这个决定大错特错
from a business standpoint.
我知道了
Noted.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
-给我  -对不起
- Give me that. - I'm sor-- sorry.
对不起  对不起
Sorry, sorry!
饶命
Uncle!
我的天
Jesus!
你差点把我吓尿了
God, you scared the shit out of me.
你在做...你在这儿多久了
What are you do-- how long have you been in here?
你和女儿们回家以后
Since you and the girls got home.
她们不会来这儿找我
It's the only place they don't look for me.
我今天过得很不好
I've had a day.
好吧  我了解那种感觉
Okay, well, I know that feeling.
我曾经几周都不顺  你怎么了
I had weeks like that. What hapned?
社区聊天室刚开始有起色
Cameron's cutting all of my community rooms
卡梅伦却要全部撤掉
just when they're taking off.
而且她还客客气气的
And she was so polite about it, too.
正正经经的  我真受不了
All business. It was unbearable.
你总是说
Well, you're always saying
希望她能更专业一些
how you wished she'd be more professional.
是啊  但不是来对付我
Yeah, but not against me.
我们应该是同一阵线的
We're supposed to be partners.
不如你脱掉衣服真正泡个澡吧
Why don't you get undressed and take an actual bath, okay?
我哄女儿们睡觉再给你叫个外卖
I'll put the girls to bed and I'll order takeout for you
-你想吃什么我就点什么  -我不饿
- from whatever restaurant you want. - No, I'm not hungry.
你还记得
Do you remember
你第一次打开巨人电脑时
how you felt the first time you powered on the Giant
-就知道它会非比寻常的那种感觉吗  -记得
- and you knew it was something special? - Yeah.
第一个用户
Well, I felt the same way
进入我的社区聊天室时我也是这种感觉
when the first user entered my Community room.
就好像...
It was like--
我说不好  就像生孩子
I don't know, it was like giving birth.
你懂吗  我知道听起来很疯狂
You know? I know that sounds crazy.
一点也不疯狂
Look, it doesn't sound crazy at all.
你创造了它  它就是你的孩子
Look, you created it. It is your baby.
是啊
Yeah.
你能理解我真好
It's really nice that you get it.
我不知道  我不知道我能不能行
I don't know. I don't know if I'm cut out for this.
你可以的  好吗
Hey, look, you can do this, okay?
你是当局者迷  但我看得出来
You're too lost to see it, but I can see it.
别管卡梅伦的想法
Forget what Cameron thinks.
这是个好创意
This is a big idea.
你一定要坚持下去
You have to see it through.
那又有什么用呢  就算...
But what's the point? Even if--
就算我们把所有XT重新上线运转
even if we get all the XTs back up and running,
也没法依靠那个脆弱的自制网络长期维持下去
we can't survive long-term on a rickety, homemade network.
听着  你会想到办法的
Look, you'll-- you'll figure something out.
我要是在这儿躲到女儿们上床
Would I be a terrible mother
是不是个糟糕透顶的妈妈
if I stayed in here until the girls went to sleep?
是的
Yes.
你这么晚还出来
You're-- you're out late.
或是很早  看你的睡眠时间了
Or early, depending on your sleep schedule.
是啊  白天电话一直响
Uh, yeah, I couldn't get any work done
闹得我什么事都没做完
during the day with the phones ringing,
所以...我就是来买点零食
so I-- I'm just here to get snacks.
-嗯  -杂货店嘛...
- Right, yeah... - Grocery store, so...
-我不知道你在这儿工作  -其实是来卧底的
- I didn't know you worked here. - I'm actually here undercover.
为我们的游戏做点调查
Um, for our games. I'm doing some research.
已经想到个点子了  《理货小哥》
I got one already. "Stock Boy."
要求玩家
It's where the players have
在十分钟内理好所有架子
10 minutes to try and stock all the shelves
还要避开来找成人纸尿裤的老人
while dodging senior citizens on the hunt for adult diapers.
我高中时在这儿工作过
I used to work here in high school
所以经理给我安排了几轮班
and the manager let me pick up a couple shifts.
当然  就...
Yeah, of course, it's-- -
就到我的股份增值的时候
It's just till the shares are worth something.
很好
That's great.
也不是...非常好
I-- I mean, it's not, like, great.
火焰糖球
Yeah, the FireBall Jawbreakers,
在6号通道尽头的底层
they're at the bottom shelf at the end of aisle six,
好又多在同一道的中间
and the Good & Plentys are halfway down the same aisle,
不过是在右边
but they're on the right.
不难注意到  你身后总是留下一堆包装纸
It's hard to miss. You always leave a trail of wrappers in your wake.
好  好的
Cool. Uh... right.
一会儿见
I'll see you in a few.
-好  -好
- Yep. - Okay.
我的条件是  首先  我说了算
Here are my terms. First off, I'm in charge.
第二  我免费帮你
Second, I'll provide my services for free
但穆特尼要作你的第一个客户  好吗
in exchange for Mutiny being your first client, all right?
第三  这是试点工程
And third, dude, this is a pilot program.
给我个折扣
I expect a discounted rate.
你在穆特尼搞砸了什么事
So, what did you screw up over at Mutiny?
没有  我只是想帮我老婆
Nothing. I'm just trying to help out my wife.
我问问清楚
All right, let me get this straight.
唐娜问过你卡梅伦的公司
Donna asked you if Cameron's company
能不能做我的试点工程吗
could be my pilot program.
他们走投无路了
They're desperate.
也不至于  他们公司状况很好
They're not desperate. Look, the company's in great shape.
我们成交还是怎样
Do we have a deal or not?
好吧  我列了个设备列表
All right, I put together an equipment list.
告诉你  修改主机配置以安装分时系统
Just so you know, converting the mainframes for time-sharing
不是扳个开关那么简单
isn't as easy as just flipping a switch.
贝尔公司推出
可用同一根电话线传输多个用户的数据的机器
光设置T1连接  就需要几天时间
I mean, the T-1 connections alone are gonna take a few days.
我已经装了3根T1高速线进去了
I already had three T-1 high-speed lines installed.
你只需要给连接好
I just need you to finish the connections
再装上IBM的分时运行功能就好
and install IBM's time-sharing option.
也是分时运行系统
好吧  我们应该用密歇根终端系统All right. Well, we should use Michigan Terminal Systems.
比IBM的可靠的多
You know, it's much more reliable than IBM.
你今晚能开工吗
Could you do it tonight?
-为什么要今晚  -行不行吧  戈登
- Why tonight? - Can you do it or can't you, Gordon?
可以  可以
Yeah, yeah, I could do it.
很好  你拿上这些东西
Great, why don't you grab this stuff
我们8点在街对面的酒吧见
and meet me at the bar across the street at 8:00?
你干吗不拿上东西  然后8点在酒吧见我
Why don't you grab this stuff and meet me at the bar at 8:00?
好吧  在我滚蛋之前要问一下
Okay, um, before I go screw myself,
你上次打电话
when was the last time that
计算机服务的老板接听是什么时候
you got the head of CompuServe on the phone?
还有  我们不是计算机服务
Also, we're not CompuServe!
怎么
Yeah?
-我好像来得不巧  -没事  请进
- This a bad time? - Huh? No, no, come in.
就是在做客服
Just doing some customer service.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
你用过穆特尼社区吗
Have you ever used Mutiny Community?
用过
Yeah.
-你想问什么  -这就是我的问题
- What's your question? - That. That was my question.
我觉得你决定放弃它之前  至少应该试试
I just thought you should try it before you decide to drop it.
但既然你用过了  那你来决定吧
But you have, so I'll leave it to you.
好吧
Okay.
你最喜欢哪个聊天室
What's your favorite room?
什么
What?
你最喜欢的聊天室  大家都有所偏好
Your favorite room. All the guys have one.
我就想问问
I'm just curious.
我知道社区是什么
I know what Community is.
恕我直言  我觉得你不知道
With respect, I disagree.
只是单纯的文本
It's simple text
没有图像  也毫无可玩性
with no graphical capability or playability.
我说错了吗
Am I wrong?
代码虽然简单
The code might not be revolutionary,
但用户间的互动
but the interactions between users
是一种全新的交流方式
are a completely new way of communicating.
人们可以在网络上释放出真实的自我
People can be more authentic online than in real life,
这会让人上瘾
and that is addictive.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我会试试社区
I'll give a spin in Community.
但别指望我会改主意
Just don't expect me to change my mind.
是因为你不喜欢
Because you just don't like it
还是因为它不是你的主意
or because it didn't come from you?
待定
成交
能重开暖气了吗
Can we turn the heat back on now?
得了  去买条新羊绒裙子吧  小妞
Aw, come on. Get yourself a new wool skirt, milady.
我们又争取回一个用户
We just got back another subscriber.
我觉得我们该庆祝一下
I think we should celebrate.
这是卡梅伦买来今晚喝的
Cameron bought those for tonight.
是啊  我们还在上班
Oh, right, we're still on the clock.
没有吧
Or are we?
当心
Heads up.
喝  喝  喝
Drink! Drink! Drink!
你全洒在我的股份上了  让我怎么活
You're spilling on my shares. How am I gonna feed myself?
老天啊
God, man.
您想跟卡梅豪伊私聊吗
是
卡梅豪伊 :        你在忙什么
私聊
汤兰顿 :           其实  我刚要睡着
汤兰顿 :        其实  我刚要睡着
卡梅豪伊 :     我不好
汤兰顿 :        没事啦  我新做了个3D的东西要给你看
汤兰顿 :           没事啦  我新做了个3D的东西要给你看
卡梅豪伊 :        等我把那混蛋毁掉的游戏全部重新配置好就过去看
卡梅豪伊 :            等我把那混蛋毁掉的游戏全部重新配置好就过去看
汤兰顿 :            别这样  戈登=唐娜的丈夫
汤兰顿 :                别这样  戈登=唐娜的丈夫
卡梅豪伊 :            不  戈登=让唐娜生了两个孩子害她拖家带口的男人
卡梅豪伊 :           不  戈登=让唐娜生了两个孩子害她拖家带口的男人
那条信息发送给所有人了
Um, that went to everyone.
-你说什...  -所有人
- What do you-- - Everyone.
我知道现在告诉你不太合适
I know this isn't the best time to tell you this,
但免得你以后再搞错
but for future reference,
D+shift+感叹号
the letter D plus the shift key plus exclamation mark
是"发送至所有人"
means "direct to all."
卡梅豪伊 :     不  戈登=让唐娜生了两个孩子害她拖家带口的男人
好了  东西都放在后备箱里呢
All right, I got everything in my trunk.
我没时间把它们捆好
I didn't have time to tape them all to one sheet,
替我开个报销单  好吗
so fill out the expense report for me, will ya?
你们有锚牌蒸汽啤酒吗
Hey, any chance you guys carry Anchor Steam?
那随便给我杯啤酒吧
Well, uh, give me whatever's that's on tap.
我身上只有这些了
That's all I got on me.
剩下的周末再给你
I'll give you the rest by the end of the week.
你干吗自己贴钱啊
Why are you reimbursing me with your own money?
你给我搞到通行证了吗
Did you get me that security badge?
你不需要通行证
You don't need a security badge.
-为什么  -都下班了
- Why not? - It's after hours.
正因为这样我才需要通行证啊
Isn't that all the more reason I need a security badge?
乔
Joe?
我也想按章办事
I tried to do this all by the book,
但有个白痴碍事
but I was getting stonewalled by some half-wit lifer
-他连什么是被动收入  -难以置信
- who couldn't even understand the concept - Oh, unbelievable.
都不懂
of passive income.
我觉得你就不懂什么是诚实
Look, I don't think you understand the concept of good faith.
我知道如果我告诉你这是我个人的主意
I knew if I told you I was doing this on the side,
-你肯定会小题大做  -"个人的主意"
- you'd make a big deal about it. - Oh, "on the side."
这就是大事
No, it is a big deal.
你为什么不去跟你准岳父说
Why didn't you take this to your future father-in-law?
这主意很棒啊
Okay? It's a great idea.
他不会像你那样理解我的设想
He wouldn't get my vision the way you did.
只是我的一席空话
It would just be words.
我需要证据  才能让他相信我
I needed evidence to back it up so he could trust me.
要赢得他的信任  最棒的办法
And what better way to earn his trust
莫过于大半夜闯进他的公司
than to break into his building in the middle of the night
摆弄他的最先进的主机
and mess with his state-of-the-art mainframe?
-这招数更好  -好吧
- It's a better play. - Oh, it's a better play.
-莎拉知道吗  -她今晚在奥斯汀过夜
- Does Sara know about this? - She's in Austin for the night.
好啊  那我们打给她
Mm, all right, well, let's call her up,
跟她说说我们要做什么
tell her what we're about to do,
如果她不介意  那我就乐意帮忙
and if she's okay with it, then I'm happy to help.
好啊  我们先打给唐娜
Okay, after we call up Donna
告诉她  她今后要从我这儿租网了
and tell her that she'll be leasing her new network from me.
听着  我和唐娜
Listen, Donna and I,
我们从不隐瞒彼此什么
we don't hide anything from each other.
好啊  那我们打给她
Great, let's call her up.
我很想跟她打个招呼呢
I'd love to say hi.
我现在真想揍你一拳
You know, I'd like to punch you in the face right now.
自便
Be my guest.
好吧  我撒谎了  我不会用社区
Okay, I lied. I don't know how to use Community.
你如果都不尊重我
How is anybody supposed to respect me
别人怎么会尊重我
when you're disrespecting me?
-这你想到了吗  -没有
- Did you think about that? - No.
你跟汤姆聊天的时候想到这一点了吗
Did you think about that at all when you were messaging with Tom?
没有  老实说  我什么都没想
No, I-I... honestly, I wasn't thinking at all.
-是啊  -你要我去跟所有人道歉吗
- Yeah. - Do you want me to go apologize to everyone?
不  别那么做  什么都别做
No, don't do that. Don't do anything.
唐娜  你就没有私下里
Donna, haven't you ever said something shitty
说过你在公共场合绝不会说的关于别人的坏话吗
about somebody in private that you'd never say in public?
言不由衷的坏话
That you don't really mean?
重点不在这儿
That's not what we're talking about.
你如果对戈登有意见  你跟我说
If you have a problem with Gordon, you come to me.
你不可以在我背后议论
You don't talk about it behind my back
而且你永远不可以谈论我的孩子
and you don't ever... don't ever talk about my kids.
-你没事吧  -嗯
- Whoa, are you okay? - Yeah.
-要水吗  -不用  我没事
- Do you want water? - No, I'm fine.
我觉得我还染上琼妮的流感了
I just think on top of everything else I have Joanie's flu.
对不起
I'm really sorry.
你知道你和汤姆私聊时
You know that feeling of freedom that you had
那种自在的感觉
when you're sending private messages with Tom?
那种有个地方可以跟人
That feeling that you had a place to go
说些当面不会说的话的感觉
where you could say things you wouldn't say in person?
那
That...
那就是社区的价值所在
that is the value of Community.
需要你们
I need you in there.
我们在为《字节》杂志的广告拍集体照
We're doing the group photo for the "Byte" ad.
我在采取高中照全班照的方式
I'm doing a take on class photos from high school,
但没了你俩  感觉就像85届节欲俱乐部
and without you two, it looks like the abstinence club of 1985.
好了  伙计们  大家把啤酒放下
Okay, guys. Guys, guys, can we put down the beer
就忍五分钟
for, like... just, like, five minutes?
五分钟  你站这里
Five minutes, okay? Okay, you're gonna come right here.
这里  放那边
Right here. Put it down over there.
过来  排好
Come here, come here. Get in line.
神童  站这儿  好了
Wonderboy, right here. Okay, here we go.
好了
Nice and...
抱歉  站好队
Sorry. Stand there in the line.
看看
Take a look at this.
好了  慢着  博迪呢  伙计们
Okay. Wait, where's... where's Bodie, guys?
他蹲厕所呢  汤姆
Eh, he's in the bathroom, Tom.
蹲厕所  谁去叫他一下啊
He's in the bathroom? Well, can someone go get him?
拜托  伙计们  这里简直像托儿所
Please? Jesus, guys, I feel like I'm running a nursery here.
好了  严肃点  把啤酒放下
Okay, tighten up, guys. Put down the beer.
好了  不行
Okay, here we... no, no, no, no, no.
你得站到中间来
Here, you gotta come front and center.
唐娜  中间  好吗
Donna, front and center. Okay?
好了  就这儿  真棒  谢谢
Okay? Right here. That's great. Thank you.
好了  不错  数到三
Okay, this is looking good, guys. Okay, on three.
笑起来  一  二  三
Big smiles. One, two, three.
唐娜  卡梅伦  简直太棒了
Donna, Cameron, that is perfect.
你俩嘴角能不能上扬一点
Do you mind lifting the corners of your mouths?
上扬一大点  好吗  我拍了
Like a whole lot? Okay? Here we go.
好了  数到三  莱夫  你挡住神童了
Okay, on three. Lev, Lev, you're blocking Wonderboy.
-好吗  -不戴眼镜我听不清
- Okay? - I can't hear without my glasses.
不戴眼镜听不清啊
You can't hear without your glasses.
这衣服是我新买的
I just bought this shirt!
好了  神童  神童
Okay, guys. Wonderboy! Wonderboy!
神童  别闹了  好吗
Wonderboy, just stop, okay?
大家别闹了  你们站好吧
Everybody just stop. Can we just get together?
就一分钟
Just for, like, one minute?!
很好  笑开点  好吗
Good, great. Big smiles, all right?
天呐  一  二...
Jesus. One, two...
-这可好  谢了  -我看上去怎么样
- That's great. That's great. Thanks. - Did it look good?
难看死了  真好
Complete disaster. That's good.
把酒给我
Give me that beer. Give me that beer.
小心
Watch out!
趴下
Get down!
小心
Watch it!
小心  他是红队的
Watch out, he's on red team!
打他  那边呢
Get him! He's over there.
-卡尔  -嗯
- Hey, Carl? - Uh, yeah?
你把社区下线了吗
Did you take down Community yet?
没呢
Oh, um, no,
但我今晚走之前会弄的
but I promise I'll do it before I leave tonight.
我现在挺清醒的
And I'm pretty sober, so...
不用了
No, it's...
再留几天吧
just leave it up for a few more days, okay?
好极了  我现在根本不清醒
Okay, great, that's good 'cause I'm not at all sober, so...
-谢了  回见  -来人了
- Thanks. See ya. - Man comin' in.
来人了  掩护我
Coming in! Cover me!
快加入游戏
Get your head in the game.
15秒后开始  红队
15 seconds. Red team.
15秒后我就开始打你了
You got 15 seconds before I shoot you.
小心了
Look out, look out!
上
Okay, go.
好嘞
Okay, got it.
小心  桌子后面  打他
Careful, behind the desk. Behind the desk! Get him! Get him!
趴下
Get down. Get down.
-走廊安全  -天呐
- Hallway's clear. - Oh, God!
-他们打中我了  他打中我了  -不
- They shot me! He got me. - No!
-没子弹了  -你死定了
- Out of ammo. - You're dead.
打中他了
Got him!
-你的枪归我了  -给我弹药
- Got your guns, babe. - Ammo.
-用他的枪  -主啊  救救我
- Here, take his gun. - Lord, help me.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
卡梅伦  小心  找掩护
Cameron, watch out! Take cover!
你很想开枪吧
Oh, you wanna shoot me so bad.
为什么  因为你不给工资了
Why? Because you stopped paying us,
却还是使唤我们吗
but you're still riding all our asses?
-嗯  差不多吧  -而且你专横
- Yeah, something along those lines. - And you're imperious
固执  而且你从不给出有建设性的批评
and you're stubborn and you never, ever give constructive criticism.
知道了  我是个坏老板
I get it, I'm a horrible boss.
其实  这些我都很喜欢
Actually, I like all that about you.
你为什么还不开枪
So... why haven't you taken a shot at me yet?
不知道
I don't know.
因为我真的很想开枪
'Cause I sure as hell want to,
但我又希望你能留在游戏里
but I also kind of want you in the game.
是吗
Yeah?
-就是这个  -什么
- That's it. - What's it?
这个
This.
我们在线上创造这个游戏
We create this game online.
-我们争不过卡带游戏  对吧  -嗯
- We can't compete with box games, right? - Yeah.
但我们的优势在于联网
But what we have going for us is we're networked.
不要再做射击坦克或机器人的游戏了
Instead of shooting at a tank or a robot,
我们让用户能在我们的网络上射击其他用户
what if you're shooting at another user on our network?
人类玩家不像
I mean, human players aren't
计算机生成的敌人那么好猜透
predictable like a computer-generated enemy.
如果你能
I mean, how cool would it be
直视对方的眼睛  那多酷啊
if you're looking right at them, eye to eye?
-你的朋友也是你的敌人  -对
- Your friend is also your enemy. - Yeah.
谁不会偶尔想打自己的朋友啊
I mean, who doesn't want to shoot their friend sometimes?
但是我们怎么在网络上构建图像
But how would we do the graphics over the network?
我们得...一半靠玩家电脑处理
We'd have to do... build half of it on the C64
-另一半通过网络传输  -对
- and then the other half on our network. - Yes.
康懋达64电脑
C64足以处理场景图像
And the C64, that can manage the scenery graphics
和玩家动作  我们来处理玩家位置
and the player movement, and we can manage the user's location,
决定他们能否看到彼此
whether or not they can... they can see each other,
以及分数  等等
the score, all that sort of thing.
我们还得建立一套
And we'd have to build a protocol
玩家和我们的电脑间的协议
between the user's computer and ours
这样我们就能控制游戏图像了
so that we can control the game graphics.
嗯  当然
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
做成简短  通用的指令
As long as they're short, encoded instructions.
嗯  以免拖慢游戏速度
Yeah, to keep the game speed up and...
天呐  我是你队友啊  混蛋
Jesus! I'm on your team, asshole.
别闹  我们工作呢
Excuse me, we're trying to work in here.
-兰顿呢  -他死了  我打死了他
- Hey, where's Rendon? - He's dead. I shot him.
回去告诉他  他女伴打电话来了
Well, go back and tell him that his date's on the phone.
汤姆  女人找
Yo, Tom, a lady's on the phone.
我得去了
Uh, I gotta go.
好吧  开心点
Okay, have fun.
真绅士啊
You're such a gentleman.
他往那边去了  打他
He went back that way! Get him!
再过两小时就有人来上班了
People are gonna be here in two hours.
好吧
Yeah, well...
还要多久
How much longer?
出门旅行时我女儿就爱这么问
You sound like my girls on a road trip.
你比以前慢了
You're slower than you used to be.
你要我像组装巨人专业版那样组装这个吗
Well, you want me to slap this thing together like the Giant Pro?
就快插好了
I'm almost done slotting.
然后还得上传虚拟主机
Then I gotta upload the hosting
和分时运行系统  这样...
and time-sharing options that'll switch the TSO...
那事不怪你  巨人专业版
That's not on you, the Giant Pro.
没有哪台机器能满足每个客户的一切需求
No one machine can be everything to every customer.
我们一定程度上都在瞎猜
We're all guessing in the dark to a certain extent.
嗯  我完全不知道客户想要什么
Yeah, well, I have no idea what consumers want
也猜够了
and I'm sick and tired of trying to figure it out.
知道吗
You know, I wish...
真希望大家能告诉我他们究竟想要什么
I wish people would just tell me exactly what they want
我就会去给他们搭建了
and then I would go and build it.
就像给客人订制西装的裁缝
Like a tailor making a custom suit.
是啊  我什么都会建
Exactly. I can build anything.
我再去给你拿瓶可乐
Let me grab you a fresh Coke.
你怎么了
Hey, hey, what happened?
没事...我就是...
Oh, nothing. I just, uh...
我摔倒了  一定是绊倒了
I just fell. I must've tripped.
-绊在哪了  -脚卡在柜子边上了
- On what? - I caught my foot on the edge of the cabinet here.
我没事的
Look, I'm fine. I'm fine.
我们继续吧  都快日出了
Let's just keep going. Look, the sun's almost up.
戈登  你看上去不太好
Hey, Gordon, you don't look so good.
你是我妈啊
What are you, my mother?
多谢给我拿汽水
Thanks for the soda.
你来得好早
Well, you're here early.
嗯  有个人总不在家
Yeah, this one fella was never at home.
只能趁他要去上班
Only way to catch him was in his car,
正从车库里往外倒车的时候堵他
in the garage, as he pulled out on his way to work.
-来  -你知道...
- Here. - You know...
好了
All right.
我不会再求你来这儿工作了
I'm not gonna ask you to work here again, okay?
我告诉你
I'm telling you.
你明天就来上班  这里就是你的办公室
You start tomorrow. This is your office.
不用说  这里执行不闭门政策
It has an open-door policy, obviously,
因为这根本是个厨房
because it is the kitchen.
你的第一项任务
Your first task...
是帮我把这家公司做得更好
is I need you to help me run this company better.
是  女士
Yes, ma'am.
真的  我想做得更好
I mean it. I want to be better at this.
我23时  我在卡迪夫的工作就一项
When I was 23, my job at Cardiff was to do one thing...
把手持无线电设备装箱待运
put the hand radio kits in the box for shipment.
就这样  贴标签都不是我负责
That's it. Wasn't even responsible for labeling them.
我就负责装箱  然后下班喝酒去
I just boxed 'em, punched out, and drank beer.
你会做好的
You'll get there.
什么时候啊
When?
我把相片洗好了
I got the film developed from the... yeah.
不知道这些能不能...
I don't know... I don't know if there's anything...
用得上
like, usable in there.
我们打过招呼  但还没握过手
We've howdied, but we ain't shook.
-约翰·博斯沃思  -汤姆·兰顿
- John Bosworth. - Tom Rendon.
天呐
Oh, my God.
这张就是广告照
And there's your ad right there.
嗯
Yeah.
《跟朋友玩游戏》  标题就叫这个
"Play with friends." That's the tag.
你心情不错啊
You're in a good mood.
约会很顺利吧
Your date must have gone well.
一点也不顺利
Uh, it was terrible, actually.
我提前走了
I had to cut it short.
她不肯献身吗
Aw, she wouldn't put out?
真好笑啊
Funny. So funny.
不是
No, I, uh...
我一直在想游戏的事
well, I couldn't stop thinking about the game.
我也是
I know, me, too.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
-没事吧  -嗯
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
好
Okay.
唐娜  你还要在里面待多久啊
Donna, how much longer you gonna be in there?
说不好
I don't know.
或许你该去看看医生
You know, maybe you should go see a doctor, you know?
就确保一下不是什么大病
Just to rule out anything serious.
不用  我觉得我就是染上琼妮的流感了
No, I think I... I must've just got what Joanie had.
我有好消息
Well, I got some great news
你听了一定会好受的
that I think'll make you feel better.
记得我昨晚去给人做咨询吧
You know that consulting gig I did last night?
我说服了
Well, I convinced,
我在那边的联络人
uh, my contact over there
把他们的网络每小时3美元租给穆特尼
to lease their network to Mutiny for $3 an hour.
这种好事独一无二啊
Okay, nobody's getting that kind of deal.
你能管理数千个社区聊天室了
You'll be able to run thousands of Community rooms.
这困境逆转得怎么样
How's that for turning lemons into lemonade?
唐娜  你听到了吗
Donna, did you hear me?
嗯
Yeah.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这太棒了
Um, that is amazing news.
你在吐吗
Are you throwing up?
嗯
Yeah.
给我点时间好吗
Can you give me a sec?
嗯
Yeah, sure.
我就在厨房
I'll be in the kitchen.